Guide to the David Newton Henderson Papers, 1930-1976 RL.00528
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Committee Files Series
  - POST OFFICE AND CIVIL SERVICE COMMITTEE
    - Non-Subcommittee Files
      - Postal Reform
        - Right to Work, 1970.Correspondence and lobbying material from constituents and interested parties concerning the Henderson Amendment. (Box 57)
        - Star Route Amendment, 1969 (Box 58)
      - Postal Service Contract, 1971 (Box 58)
      - Postal Service Organization and Management, 1972 (Box 58)
      - Postal Strike, 1970 (Box 58)
      - Postmaster General Meeting, 1971 (Box 58)
      - Removal of Copy Machines, 1975 (Box 58)
      - Retirement, 1971-1973 (Box 58)
      - Schedules, 1974-1976 (Box 58)
      - Special, 1962-1966 (Box 59)
      - Sunny Point Terminal, 1971-1972 (Box 59)
      - Supergrades, 1966-1968 (Box 59)
      - Supergrades and Wage Board Pay, 1968 (Box 59)
      - Transportation, Department of. Supergrades, 1966 (Box 59)
      - Unsolicited Samples, 1972 (Box 59)
      - Wage Board, 1971-1972 (Box 59)
      - Wage Board Employees, 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEE
    General note
    Name changed in 1975 to Public Works and Transportation
    - Public Works, 1963-1976 (Box 60-66)
    - Subcommittee Files
      - Aviation Subcommittee, 1975-1976 (Box 67)
        - Hearings and Reports, 1973-1976.Printed material about aviation planning and committee hearings concerning aviation regulation. (Box 68-71)
      - Economic Development Subcommittee, 1974-1976 (Box 72)
      - Energy Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 72)
      - Flood Control Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 72)
      - Investigations and Reviews Subcommittee, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 72)
      - Public Buildings and Grounds Subcommittee, 1963, 1974-1976 (Box 73)
      - Rivers and Harbors Subcommittee, 1963, 1972 (Box 73)
      - Rivers and Harbors, and Flood Control Subcommittees, 1965 (Box 73)
      - Roads Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 73)
      - Surface Transportation Subcommittee, 1975-1976 (Box 74)
      - Transportation Subcommittee, 1974-1974 (Box 74)
      - Water Resources Subcommittee, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 74)
    - Non-Subcommittee Files
      - Army Corps of Engineers Jurisdiction, 1975 (Box 75)
      - Federal Aid Highway Legislation, 1974-1976 (Box 75)
      - Federal Protective Service Legislation, 1975 (Box 75)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1976 (Box 75)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Act. Henderson Amendment, 1976 (Box 75)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Act. Hearings and Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 76)
      - Jackson Purchase Rural Cooperative Cooperation, 1965 (Box 77)
      - Motorcycle Helmet Issue, 1975-1976 (Box 77)
      - Schedules, 1974, 1976 (Box 77)
      - Special, 1963-1964 (Box 77)
      - Truck Weight-Width Regulation, 1968 (Box 77)
      - Water Pollution Control, 1971-1972 (Box 77)
- Correspondence: Answer Copies Series
  This series provides a complete record of Henderson's outgoing correspondence from 1968 through 1976. These files are composed of second carbon copies of outgoing mail. The first copy was attached to the correspondent's letter and filed away to its appropriate place. For each year the letters are filed within alphabetical folders such as all surnames beginning with letters Sl-So are in a folder so labeled. Within the folder labeled Sl-So, the letters are arranged not alphabetically but chronologically during the year.
  - 1968: (Box 78)
    - A-D (Box 78)
    - E-K (Box 79)
    - L-Q (Box 80)
    - R-Z (Box 81)
  - 1969: (Box 82)
    - A-B (Box 82)
    - C-F (Box 83)
    - G-I (Box 84)
    - J-Mh (Box 85)
    - Mi-Q (Box 86)
    - R-S (Box 87)
    - T-Z (Box 88)
  - 1970: (Box 89)
    - A-B (Box 89)
    - C-F (Box 90)
    - G-I (Box 91)
    - J-Mh (Box 92)
    - Mi-Q (Box 93)
    - R-S (Box 94)
    - T-Z (Box 95)
  - 1971: (Box 96)
    - A-B (Box 96)
    - C-F (Box 97)
    - G-I (Box 98)
  - 1971: (Box 99)
    - J-Mh (Box 99)
    - Mi-Q (Box 100)
    - R-S (Box 101)
    - T-Z (Box 102)
  - 1972: (Box 103)
    - A-B (Box 103)
    - C-F (Box 104)
    - G-J (Box 105)
    - K-M (Box 106)
    - N-R (Box 107)
    - S-U (Box 108)
    - V-Z (Box 109)
  - 1973: (Box 110)
    - A-B (Box 110)
    - C-F (Box 111)
    - G-J (Box 112)
    - K-M (Box 113)
    - N-R (Box 114)
    - S-U (Box 115)
    - V-Z (Box 116)
  - 1974: (Box 117)
    - A-B (Box 117)
    - C-F (Box 118)
    - G-J (Box 119)
    - K-M (Box 120)
    - N-R (Box 121)
    - S-T (Box 122)
    - U-Z (Box 123)
  - 1975: (Box 124)
    - A-B (Box 124)
    - C-F (Box 125)
    - 1975: (Box 126)
    - G-J (Box 126)
    - K-M (Box 127)
    - N-R (Box 128)
    - S-T (Box 129)
    - U-Z (Box 130)
  - 1976: (Box 131)
    - A-D (Box 131)
    - E-L (Box 132)
    - M-R (Box 133)
    - S-Z (Box 134)
- County Project Files Series
  Contains correspondence, notes, newspaper clippings and printed material concerning projects and local affairs in the Third Congressional District. Much of the material relates to projects such as urban renewal, housing developments, anti-poverty programs, water and sewer projects, the construction of recreational facilities, hospitals, and public buildings, etc. Henderson's correspondence with federal agencies, local officials, and interested constituents reflects his position as an intermediary between local interests and federal financing. The County Project Files contain a considerable amount of material from the office of Graham H. Barden. This material is indicated in the inventory by dates prior to 1961.
  - Bladen County
    - Bladen Technical Institute, Dublin, 1973-1974 (Box 135)
    - Bladenboro, 1973-1974 (Box 135)
    - Bladenboro Medical Center, 1974 (Box 135)
    - Clarkton, 1973-1974 (Box 135)
    - East Bladen High School. ROTC, 1972 (Box 135)
    - Elizabethtown, 1973-1974 (Box 135)
    - Schools, 1971 (Box 135)
    - Miscellany, 1971-1974 (Box 135)
  - Carteret County
    - Area Redevelopment Administration, Dept. of Commerce and Accelerated Public Works Program Projects, 1961-1965.Federally-funded programs for areas of high-unemployment. (Box 135)
    - Atlantic. Harbor of Refuge, 1970-1971 (Box 135)
    - Atlantic Beach, 1961-1972 (Box 136)
    - Baptist Housing for the Elderly, Inc., Morehead City, 1961 (Box 136)
    - Barden's Inlet, 1935-1971 (Box 136)
    - Beaufort, 1954-1972 (Box 136)
    - Beaufort. Housing and Urban Development, Department of. Grants, 1966-1972 (Box 137)
    - Beaufort Armory, 1958 (Box 137)
    - Beaufort Harbor, 1948-1971 (Box 137)
    - Beaufort-Morehead City Airport, 1961-1967 (Box 137)
    - Beaufort Technical Institute, 1972 (Box 137)
    - Bogue Banks Water and Sewer Corporation, Beaufort, 1971 (Box 137)
    - Bogue Field, 1953-1971 (Box 137)
    - Bogue Inlet, 1940 (Box 137)
    - Bogue Sound. Channel and Basin, 1966-1971 (Box 137)
    - Brett Bay, 1956-1957 (Box 137)
    - Brooks Creek, 1956-1958 (Box 137)
    - Calico Creek Harbor of Refuge, Morehead City, 1970-1971 (Box 138)
    - Cape Carteret, 1969 (Box 138)
    - Cape Lookout. Rural Electrification Administration, 1968-1971 (Box 138)
    - Cape Lookout National Seashore, 1961-1971 (Box 138)
    - Cape Lookout National Seashore. Employment, 1967 (Box 138)
    - Cape Lookout National Seashore. Legislative Action, House of Representatives Bill #1784, 1965-1966 (Box 138)
    - Cape Lookout National Seashore. Legislative Action, North Carolina, 1969 (Box 138)
    - Cat Island, 1956-1957 (Box 139)
    - Cedar Island Bay, 1956-1965 (Box 139)
    - Cedar Island Wildlife Refuge, 1964-1969 (Box 139)
    - Cedar Point-Pettifords Creek Bay. Recreation Centers, 1962 (Box 139)
    - Coastal Crafts Project, 1968.Proposed program by Carteret County Community Action to relieve local unemployment. (Box 139)
    - Community Action, 1966-1974.Federally-funded social works program dealing with low-income families, especially alcoholism, housing, medical care, family planning, adult education, job training and headstart programs. (Box 139)
    - Core Creek Bridge, 1963-1969 (Box 139)
    - Core Sound Project, 1934-1972 (Box 139)
    - Cross Creek Channel, 1945-1951 (Box 139)
    - Davis, 1963 (Box 140)
    - Drum Inlet, 1935-1971 (Box 140)
    - Duke University Marine Lab, Beaufort, 1967-1969 (Box 140)
    - Environmental Science Services Administration East Coast Laboratory, Radio Island, 1966-1967 (Box 140)
    - Fishing Pier, Atlantic Beach, 1954-1959 (Box 141)
    - Fort Macon, 1967-1970 (Box 141)
    - Harker's Island, 1955-1972 (Box 141)
    - Harker's Island. Harbor of Refuge, 1967-1969 (Box 141)
    - Harker's Island Point Basin, 1946-1956 (Box 141)
    - Harlowe Creek and Clubfoot Creek, 1967 (Box 141)
    - Hurricane Survey. Bogue Inlet to Moore Inlet, 1964-1971 (Box 141)
    - Industrial Development Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 141)
    - Lennoxville Point-Big Creek Channel, 1964 (Box 141)
    - Lower Cape Fear Water and Sewer Authority, 1971 (Box 141)
    - Marine Research Laboratory, Beaufort, 1969 (Box 141)
    - Marshallberg Harbor, 1946-1959 (Box 141)
    - Marshallberg Shore Line, 1948-1958 (Box 141)
    - Morehead City, 1943-1970 (Box 141)
    - Morehead City Armory, 1961-1962 (Box 142)
    - Morehead City Harbor, 1955-1973 (Box 142)
    - Morehead City Port, 1952-1973 (Box 142)
    - Morehead City Schools, 1952-1959 (Box 142)
    - Mullets Slough, 1956 (Box 142)
    - Navy Transreceiver Radio Station, Lola, 1967-1971 (Box 143)
    - Nelson's Bay, 1956 (Box 143)
    - Newport, 1952-1972 (Box 143)
    - Newport River, 1955-1971 (Box 143)
    - North River, 1961-1971 (Box 143)
    - Ocracoke Inlet, 1972 (Box 143)
    - Outer Banks, 1959 (Box 143)
    - Patsy Lake 4-H Camp, 1960 (Box 143)
    - Pelletier Creek, 1945-1957 (Box 143)
    - Pivers Island, 1961-1962 (Box 143)
    - Salter Path. Harbor of Refuge, 1964-1972 (Box 144)
    - Schools, 1956-1971 (Box 144)
    - Sea Level Basin Project, 1967 (Box 144)
    - Sea Level Harbor, 1936-1957 (Box 144)
    - Sea Level Hospital, 1970-1971.Concerns the relocation of Sailors Snug Harbor, a home for old sailors in Staten Island, N.Y., to Sea Level, N.C., and the administration of the hospital by Duke University Medical Center. (Box 144)
    - Seafood Processing Project, 1968-1969 (Box 144)
    - Sheephead Shoals, 1957 (Box 144)
    - Taylors Creek, 1948-1959 (Box 145)
    - University of North Carolina Institute of Marine Sciences, Morehead City, 1970 (Box 145)
    - Wainwright Channel, 1951-1961 (Box 145)
    - Wallace Channel, 1940-1964 (Box 145)
    - Waterways Committee, 1961 (Box 145)
    - Miscellany, 1954-1972 (Box 146)
  - Craven County
    - Core Creek, 1945-1959 (Box 146)
    - Cove City, 1963 (Box 146)
    - Eastern North Carolina Baptist Hospital, New Bern, 1958 (Box 146)
    - Good Shepherd Hospital, New Bern, 1942-1949 (Box 146)
    - Hancock Creek and Slocum Creek, 1956-1963 (Box 146)
    - Havelock, 1961-1962 (Box 146)
    - Havelock, 1963-1967 (Box 147)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point, 1961-1976 (Box 147)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point. Housing, 1960-1961 (Box 147)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point. Laundry and Pry Cleaning Services, 1965-1966 (Box 147)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point. Naval Air Rework Facility, 1970-1971 (Box 148)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point. Overhaul and Repair Department, 1962-1967 (Box 148)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, Cherry Point. Political Affiliation of Employees, 1961 (Box 148)
    - Neuse River Dike, 1964-1970 (Box 149)
    - New Bern, 1960-1966 (Box 149)
    - New Bern, Airport, 1961-1966 (Box 149)
    - Operation Progress, 1964-1967.Community Action Program affiliated with the Office of Economic Opportunity and the North Carolina Fund, a private anti-poverty corporation with headquarters in Durham, N.C. Material concerns alleged relationship of anti-poverty programs with civil rights activism. (Box 149)
    - Schools, 1953-1967 (Box 149)
    - Steam-Electric Generating Plant, 1972-1973 (Box 150)
    - Swift Creek Flood Control, 1962-1964 (Box 150)
    - Trent River Bridge, 1952 (Box 150)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1966 (Box 150)
  - Duplin County
    - Beulaville, 1961-1963 (Box 150)
    - Beulaville Armory, 1964-1974 (Box 150)
    - Calypso, 1970 (Box 150)
    - Chinquapin. Farmers Home Administration Loan, 1966-1967 (Box 150)
    - Civil Defense Agency, Kenansville, 1973 (Box 150)
    - Duplin General Hospital, 1958-1971 (Box 150)
    - James Sprunt Institute, Kenansville, 1968-1973 (Box 150)
    - James Sprunt Institute, Kenansville. Application for National Institute of Health Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 150)
    - Kenansville, 1968-1974 (Box 150)
    - Limestone Muddy Creek Watershed, 1971 (Box 150)
    - Magnolia, 1972 (Box 151)
    - Maintenance Income Study, 1969 (Box 151)
    - Ramblewood Country Club, Inc. Farmers Home Administration Loan, 1967-1968 (Box 151)
    - Recreation Commission, 1965 (Box 151)
    - Sarceta Fire Department, 1973 (Box 151)
    - Schools, 1961-1976 (Box 151)
    - Schools. Civil Rights Compliance Plans, 1968 (Box 151)
    - Southeastern Farmers Grain Association, Warsaw, 1965-1971 (Box 151)
    - Wallace, 1960-1974 (Box 151)
    - Wallace Airport, 1961-1974 (Box 151)
    - Wallace Armory, 1957-1960 (Box 152)
    - Wallace Hospital, 1964 (Box 152)
    - Warsaw, 1974 (Box 152)
    - Warsaw. Economic Development Administration Project, 1970-1974 (Box 152)
    - Warsaw. Housing and Urban Development Project, Department of, 1971 (Box 152)
    - Warsaw. Veterans' Day Parade, 1970 (Box 152)
    - Warsaw Airport, 1964-1965 (Box 152)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1974 (Box 152)
  - Harnett County
    - Angler, 1966-1974 (Box 152)
    - Betsy Johnson Hospital, Dunn, 1969 (Box 152)
    - Black River Flood Control, 1962-1968 (Box 152)
    - Campbell College, 1969-1972 (Box 152)
    - Campbell College, 1973-1974 (Box 153)
    - Campbell College. Sewerage Project, 1969-1971 (Box 153)
    - Campbell College. The Graham Arthur Barden Chair of Political Science, Jan.-Oct. 1967 (Box 153)
    - Campbell College. The Graham Arthur Barden Chair of Political Science, Nov. 1967-1973 (Box 154)
    - Campbell College. The Graham Arthur Barden Chair of Political Science, Contributions, 1967-1972 (Box 154)
    - Central Carolina Technical Institute, 1968 (Box 155)
    - Coats, 1972 (Box 155)
    - Dunn, 1962-1974 (Box 155)
    - Dunn. Housing and Urban Development Project, Department of, 1966-1970 (Box 155)
    - Erwin, 1972-1974 (Box 155)
    - Erwin. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1969-1970 (Box 155)
    - Schools, 1964-1972 (Box 155)
    - Shawtown Community, 1969 (Box 155)
    - Miscellany, 1966-1972 (Box 155)
  - Hyde County
    - Ocracoke Inlet, 1953-1970 (Box 155)
    - Silver Lake Harbor, 1967-1968 (Box 155)
    - Johnston County (Box 155)
    - Benson, 1968-1972 (Box 156)
    - Clayton, 1969-1971 (Box 156)
    - Community Action, 1968-1974 (Box 156)
    - Four Oaks. Water and Sewer System, 1969 (Box 156)
    - Johnston County Airport, Smithfield, 1974 (Box 156)
    - Johnston County Technical Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 156)
    - Kenly, 1969-1974 (Box 156)
    - Little River Development Corporation, 1973 (Box 156)
    - Mill Creek Flood Control, 1970-1971 (Box 156)
    - Schools, 1969-1972 (Box 156)
    - Selma, 1972-1973 (Box 156)
    - Selma. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1969-1971 (Box 156)
    - Smithfield, 1972-1973 (Box 156)
    - Smithfield. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1968-1971 (Box 156)
    - Smithfield. Housing Authority, 1971 (Box 156)
    - West Smithfield Sanitary District, 1973-1974 (Box 156)
    - Miscellany, 1967-1974 (Box 157)
  - Jones County
    - Schools, 1958-1965 (Box 157)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1966 (Box 157)
  - Lee County
    - Cumnock. Farmers Home Administration Loan and Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 157)
    - Parks and Recreation Department, 1973 (Box 157)
    - Roberts Company, Sanford, 1967 (Box 157)
    - Rural Electrification Loans. Central Electric Membership Corporation, Sanford, 1966 (Box 157)
    - Sanford, 1966-1974 (Box 157)
    - Sanford. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1966-1968 (Box 157)
    - Schools, 1967-1968 (Box 157)
    - Miscellany (Box 157)
  - New Hanover County
    - Harbor Island. Saline Water Program, 1959-1960 (Box 157)
    - Masonboro Inlet, 1953-1963 (Box 157)
    - Wilmington Port, 1967-1968 (Box 157)
  - Onslow County
    - Brown and Swansboro Inlet, 1959-1960 (Box 158)
    - Camp Lejeune, 1961-1967 (Box 158)
    - Camp Lejeune, 1968-1975 (Box 159)
    - Camp Lejeune. (Box 160)
    - Barbers, 1964 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Base Exchange, 1962-1971 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Base Maintenance Shop Reorganization, 1961-1966 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Civil Service Employees, 1968 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Civilian-Military Relations, 1966-1972 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Food Service Contract, 1974 (Box 160)
    - Camp Lejeune. Garbage Disposal, 1969 (Box 161)
    - Camp Lejeune. Racial Disorder, 1969 (Box 161)
    - Camp Lejeune. Taxi Drivers, 1965 (Box 161)
    - Coastal Carolina Community College, Jacksonville, 1971-1974 (Box 161)
    - Georgetown, 1973 (Box 161)
    - Health Department, 1971 (Box 161)
    - Holly Ridge, 1974 (Box 161)
    - Holly Ridge-Camp Davis, 1970-1972 (Box 161)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of. Grants, 1969-1971 (Box 161)
    - Jacksonville, 1951-1973 (Box 161)
    - Jacksonville. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1971 (Box 161)
    - Jacksonville Airport, 1955-1974 (Box 161)
    - Jacksonville Armory, 1964-1970 (Box 162)
    - Marine Corps Air Station, New River, 1971 (Box 162)
    - New River, 1945-1951, 1961 (Box 162)
    - New River Flood Control, 1965-1966 (Box 162)
    - New River Inlet, 1935-1976 (Box 162)
    - Onslow County Fund, 1971 (Box 163)
    - Onslow County Hospital, 1971 (Box 163)
    - Schools, 1952-1971 (Box 163)
    - Sheltered Workshops, undated (Box 163)
    - Southwest Creek, 1952 (Box 163)
    - Starkys Creek, 1956 (Box 163)
    - Stone Bay, 1956 (Box 163)
    - Swansboro, 1951-1958, 1972-1974 (Box 163)
    - Richlands, 1955-1960, 1972 (Box 163)
    - Thiokol Corporation Project, 1961 (Box 163)
    - Topsail Beach, 1972-1974 (Box 163)
    - West Onslow Beach, 1971 (Box 163)
    - Miscellany, 1971-1974 (Box 163)
  - Pamlico County
    - Bay River, 1953 (Box 164)
    - Federal Crop Insurance, 1962 (Box 164)
    - Giddings Creek, 1950-1956 (Box 164)
    - Health Department, 1961-1963 (Box 164)
    - Hobucken. Coast Guard Station, 1963-1965 (Box 164)
    - Hobucken. Harbor of Refuge, 1953-1959 (Box 164)
    - Lowlands Watershed Project, 1957-1961 (Box 164)
    - Oriental, 1963 (Box 164)
    - Oriental Harbor and Smith's Creek, 1935-1956 (Box 165)
    - Oyster Creek, 1961-1965 (Box 165)
    - Schools, 1958-1965 (Box 165)
    - Vanclemere Harbor and Bay River, 1934-1939 (Box 165)
    - Miscellany, 1954-1957, 1963-1966 (Box 165)
  - Pender County
    - Burgaw, 1966-1974 (Box 166)
    - Burgaw. Radio Stations, 1961-1963 (Box 166)
    - Burgaw Airport, 1943 (Box 166)
    - Economic Development Administration, Department of Commerce, 1969-1971 (Box 166)
    - Moore's Creek National Military Park, 19611973 (Box 166)
    - New Topsail Inlet, 1966-1971 (Box 166)
    - Schools, 1959-1971 (Box 166)
    - Surf City, 1967 (Box 166)
    - Willard Agricultural Experiment Station, 1968 (Box 166)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1974 (Box 166)
  - Sampson County
    - Area Redevelopment Administration and Accelerated Public Works Program Projects, 1963-1964 (Box 167)
    - Autryville, 1974 (Box 167)
    - Carolina Power and Light Company Site, 1973 (Box 167)
    - Clinton, 1970-1974 (Box 167)
    - Clinton. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1969-1971 (Box 167)
    - Clinton. Transportation, North Carolina Department of, 1973-1974 (Box 167)
    - Clinton Day Care Center, 1965-1966.A project of Sampson County Community Action (Box 167)
    - Doctors Creek, 1970 (Box 167)
    - Farmers Dehydration, Inc., Clinton, 1969.A farmers' cooperative project to grow, dehydrate and pelletize coastal bermuda grass. Financed by FHA loan. (Box 167)
    - Garland, 1972 (Box 167)
    - Planning Board, Farmers Home Administration Grant, 1966 (Box 167)
    - Roseboro, 1970-1971 (Box 167)
    - Roseboro Armory, 1961-1970 (Box 167)
    - Salemburg, 1966-1971 (Box 167)
    - Sampson County Airport, 1961-1968 (Box 167)
    - Sampson Memorial Hospital, 1971 (Box 167)
    - Sampson Technical Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 167)
    - >Schools, 1961-1971 (Box 167)
    - Six Runs River, 1950-1970 (Box 167)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1974 (Box 167)
  - Wayne County
    - Arrington Fire Department, 1974 (Box 168)
    - Belfast Water Cooperative. Department of Housing and Urban Development Loan, 1967 (Box 168)
    - Cliffs of the Neuse State Park, 1966-1967 (Box 168)
    - Deerwood Development, 1973 (Box 168)
    - Fremont, 1961, 1972 (Box 168)
    - Fremont Armory, 1963-1968 (Box 168)
    - Goldsboro, 1954-1974 (Box 168)
    - Goldsboro. Air Service, 1959-1965 (Box 168)
    - Goldsboro. Chamber of Commerce, 1947-1958 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro. Federal Building (proposed), 1963-1969 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro. Housing and Urban Development Projects, Department of, 1967-1971 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro. Housing Authority, 1972-1974 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro. Schools, 1957-1960, 1975 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro. Veterans Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 169)
    - Goldsboro Airport, 1953-1969 (Box 169)
    - Mount Olive, 1961-1974 (Box 170)
    - Mount Olive. Housing and Urban Development, Department of, Water and Sewage Project, 1968-1970 (Box 170)
    - Mount Olive. Low-Rent Housing Units, 1970 (Box 170)
    - Mount Olive Airport, 1967-1974 (Box 170)
    - Mount Olive College, 1960-1974 (Box 170)
    - Pikeville. Sewer Project, 1967-1971 (Box 170)
    - Poverty Programs, 1966-1972 (Box 170)
    - Saulston Water System, 1969-1973 (Box 170)
    - Schools, 1961-1971 (Box 170)
    - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base, 1961-1973 (Box 171)
    - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base. Aviation Fuel Supply System, 1963-1968 (Box 171)
    - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base. Bombing Range, 1966 (Box 171)
    - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base. Garbage Disposal, 1961 (Box 171)
    - Sleepy Creek Fishing and Recreation Club, 1967 (Box 171)
    - Thoroughfare Creek Flood Control, 1966-1971 (Box 171)
    - Wayne Community College, Goldsboro, 1968-1972 (Box 171)
    - Wayne Memorial Hospital, 1969 (Box 171)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1974 (Box 172)
  - Multicounty Projects
    - Black River, 1960 (Box 172)
    - Bogue Inlet-Swaneboro Harbor, 1936-1970 (Box 172)
    - Cape Fear River Basin-New Hope Dam, 1956-1962 (Box 172)
    - Cape Fear River Basin-New Hope Dam, 1963-1971 (Box 173)
    - Coastal Growers Cooperative, 1961 (Box 173)
    - Coastal Highway, 1952-1956 (Box 173)
    - Community Action Council, Rose Hill, 1965-1974 (Box 173)
    - Croatan National Forest, 1954-1971 (Box 174)
    - Eastern Carolina Housing Authority, 1960 (Box 174)
    - Eastern North Carolina Area Airport, 1964 (Box 174)
    - Fort Bragg, 1967-1972 (Box 174)
    - Intracoastal Waterway, 1953-1958 (Box 174)
    - Lower Cape Fear Water and Sewer Authority, 1974-1975 (Box 174)
    - Lyons Swamp-White Oak Drainage District, 1964-1966 (Box 174)
    - Moccasin Swamp, 1969 (Box 175)
    - Neuse and Trent Rivers Project, 1946-1952 (Box 175)
    - Neuse River, 1930-1976 (Box 175)
    - Neuse River Economic Development Commission, 1969-1972 (Box 176)
    - New Hope Lake, 1972 - 1974 (Box 176)
    - Northeast Cape Fear River, 1935-1972 (Box 176)
    - Rockfish Creek, 1962-1972 (Box 177)
    - Sandhills Community Action Program, 1966-1968 (Box 177)
    - Southeastern Economic Development Commission, 1967-1969 (Box 177)
    - Trent River, 1949-1956 (Box 177)